✔ tests\gates\task-08-contract.mjs (100.7816ms)
✔ Given malformed-input.json, When provenance or capacity proof is unsafe, Then policy fails closed (10.8785ms)
✔ Given manual-backfill-overlap.json, When provenance or capacity proof is unsafe, Then policy fails closed (1.6347ms)
✔ Given missing-live-cadence.json, When provenance or capacity proof is unsafe, Then policy fails closed (1.5036ms)
✔ Given missing-owner-quota.json, When provenance or capacity proof is unsafe, Then policy fails closed (1.0828ms)
✔ Given missing-provenance.json, When provenance or capacity proof is unsafe, Then policy fails closed (1.3091ms)
✔ Given prompt-injection.json, When provenance or capacity proof is unsafe, Then policy fails closed (1.1302ms)
✔ Given scheduled-overlap.json, When provenance or capacity proof is unsafe, Then policy fails closed (1.0994ms)
✔ Given single-canary.json, When provenance or capacity proof is unsafe, Then policy fails closed (1.1031ms)
✔ Given stale-state.json, When provenance or capacity proof is unsafe, Then policy fails closed (3.9409ms)
✔ Given three-place-probe.json, When provenance or capacity proof is unsafe, Then policy fails closed (1.5729ms)
✔ Given unbounded-retry.json, When provenance or capacity proof is unsafe, Then policy fails closed (1.8148ms)
✔ Given an immutable receipt key, When different content is appended, Then the ledger rejects the overwrite (1.8123ms)
✔ Given an immutable D1 receipt key, When different content is persisted, Then storage rejects the overwrite (2.4314ms)
✔ Given accepted input without a D1 binding, When ingest reaches storage, Then it fails closed (44.9137ms)
✔ Given an accepted ingest, When provenance is persisted, Then its redacted canonical receipt remains queryable after the raw horizon (14.3571ms)
✔ Given four local whole-catalog runs, When capacity is evaluated without owner/live authority, Then local structure passes but production capacity is blocked (5.9806ms)
✔ Given accepted provenance metadata and a D1 binding, When the canonical ingest runs, Then it writes a durable receipt before accepting (45.3133ms)
✔ Given an existing D1 receipt, When identical content is persisted and read, Then the row is idempotent and retained (2.0789ms)
✔ Given migration 0003, When provenance storage is inspected, Then append-only receipt and derived source bindings are additive (2.1169ms)
✔ Given the durable Todo 8 receipt, When observed D1 hashes are audited, Then canonical, persisted, and readback hashes are explicit and equal (2.1396ms)
ℹ tests 21
ℹ suites 0
ℹ pass 21
ℹ fail 0
ℹ cancelled 0
ℹ skipped 0
ℹ todo 0
ℹ duration_ms 257.0322
