✔ tests\gates\task-08-contract.mjs (106.4199ms)
✔ Given malformed-input.json, When provenance or capacity proof is unsafe, Then policy fails closed (11.0064ms)
✔ Given manual-backfill-overlap.json, When provenance or capacity proof is unsafe, Then policy fails closed (1.6112ms)
✔ Given missing-live-cadence.json, When provenance or capacity proof is unsafe, Then policy fails closed (1.3658ms)
✔ Given missing-owner-quota.json, When provenance or capacity proof is unsafe, Then policy fails closed (1.1783ms)
✔ Given missing-provenance.json, When provenance or capacity proof is unsafe, Then policy fails closed (1.3026ms)
✔ Given prompt-injection.json, When provenance or capacity proof is unsafe, Then policy fails closed (1.1575ms)
✔ Given scheduled-overlap.json, When provenance or capacity proof is unsafe, Then policy fails closed (1.0583ms)
✔ Given single-canary.json, When provenance or capacity proof is unsafe, Then policy fails closed (1.1083ms)
✔ Given stale-state.json, When provenance or capacity proof is unsafe, Then policy fails closed (3.9874ms)
✔ Given three-place-probe.json, When provenance or capacity proof is unsafe, Then policy fails closed (1.2892ms)
✔ Given unbounded-retry.json, When provenance or capacity proof is unsafe, Then policy fails closed (1.2045ms)
✔ Given an immutable receipt key, When different content is appended, Then the ledger rejects the overwrite (1.6336ms)
✔ Given an immutable D1 receipt key, When different content is persisted, Then storage rejects the overwrite (2.4034ms)
✔ Given accepted input without a D1 binding, When ingest reaches storage, Then it fails closed (49.6949ms)
✔ Given an accepted ingest, When provenance is persisted, Then its redacted canonical receipt remains queryable after the raw horizon (15.7152ms)
✔ Given four local whole-catalog runs, When capacity is evaluated without owner/live authority, Then local structure passes but production capacity is blocked (2.6138ms)
✔ Given accepted provenance metadata and a D1 binding, When the canonical ingest runs, Then it writes a durable receipt before accepting (53.6318ms)
✔ Given an existing D1 receipt, When identical content is persisted and read, Then the row is idempotent and retained (2.0719ms)
✔ Given migration 0003, When provenance storage is inspected, Then append-only receipt and derived source bindings are additive (1.8548ms)
ℹ tests 20
ℹ suites 0
ℹ pass 20
ℹ fail 0
ℹ cancelled 0
ℹ skipped 0
ℹ todo 0
ℹ duration_ms 270.9969
