✔ Given malformed-input.json, When provenance or capacity proof is unsafe, Then policy fails closed (5.8771ms)
✔ Given manual-backfill-overlap.json, When provenance or capacity proof is unsafe, Then policy fails closed (1.896ms)
✔ Given missing-live-cadence.json, When provenance or capacity proof is unsafe, Then policy fails closed (1.0864ms)
✔ Given missing-owner-quota.json, When provenance or capacity proof is unsafe, Then policy fails closed (0.9107ms)
✔ Given missing-provenance.json, When provenance or capacity proof is unsafe, Then policy fails closed (1.0817ms)
✔ Given prompt-injection.json, When provenance or capacity proof is unsafe, Then policy fails closed (0.9224ms)
✔ Given scheduled-overlap.json, When provenance or capacity proof is unsafe, Then policy fails closed (0.7754ms)
✔ Given single-canary.json, When provenance or capacity proof is unsafe, Then policy fails closed (0.8986ms)
✔ Given stale-state.json, When provenance or capacity proof is unsafe, Then policy fails closed (3.1054ms)
✔ Given three-place-probe.json, When provenance or capacity proof is unsafe, Then policy fails closed (1.1513ms)
✔ Given unbounded-retry.json, When provenance or capacity proof is unsafe, Then policy fails closed (0.8882ms)
✔ Given an immutable receipt key, When different content is appended, Then the ledger rejects the overwrite (1.6672ms)
✔ Given an immutable D1 receipt key, When different content is persisted, Then storage rejects the overwrite (2.3257ms)
✔ Given accepted input without a D1 binding, When ingest reaches storage, Then it fails closed (31.8104ms)
ℹ tests 14
ℹ suites 0
ℹ pass 14
ℹ fail 0
ℹ cancelled 0
ℹ skipped 0
ℹ todo 0
ℹ duration_ms 171.4825
{
  "id": "task-08-failure",
  "verdict": "PASS",
  "actual_exit": 0,
  "assertions": [
    "provenance, quota math, overlap, backfill, and four-run cadence gates pass",
    "negative fixtures are rejected or produce the contracted fallback/NOT_RUN_BLOCKED verdict"
  ],
  "evidence": ".omo/evidence/seoul-gaja-v4-plan-review/task-8-failure.json"
}
