✔ tests\gates\task-08-contract.mjs (111.6881ms)
✔ Given malformed-input.json, When provenance or capacity proof is unsafe, Then policy fails closed (7.5474ms)
✔ Given manual-backfill-overlap.json, When provenance or capacity proof is unsafe, Then policy fails closed (1.7154ms)
✔ Given missing-live-cadence.json, When provenance or capacity proof is unsafe, Then policy fails closed (1.5134ms)
✔ Given missing-owner-quota.json, When provenance or capacity proof is unsafe, Then policy fails closed (5.0134ms)
✔ Given missing-provenance.json, When provenance or capacity proof is unsafe, Then policy fails closed (2.5045ms)
✔ Given prompt-injection.json, When provenance or capacity proof is unsafe, Then policy fails closed (3.7566ms)
✔ Given scheduled-overlap.json, When provenance or capacity proof is unsafe, Then policy fails closed (2.2093ms)
✔ Given single-canary.json, When provenance or capacity proof is unsafe, Then policy fails closed (4.3768ms)
✔ Given stale-state.json, When provenance or capacity proof is unsafe, Then policy fails closed (4.8933ms)
✔ Given three-place-probe.json, When provenance or capacity proof is unsafe, Then policy fails closed (1.4055ms)
✔ Given unbounded-retry.json, When provenance or capacity proof is unsafe, Then policy fails closed (1.3328ms)
✔ Given an immutable receipt key, When different content is appended, Then the ledger rejects the overwrite (2.7264ms)
✔ Given an immutable D1 receipt key, When different content is persisted, Then storage rejects the overwrite (2.5525ms)
✔ Given accepted input without a D1 binding, When ingest reaches storage, Then it fails closed (42.4096ms)
✔ Given an accepted ingest, When provenance is persisted, Then its redacted canonical receipt remains queryable after the raw horizon (17.003ms)
✔ Given four local whole-catalog runs, When capacity is evaluated without owner/live authority, Then local structure passes but production capacity is blocked (2.2605ms)
✔ Given accepted provenance metadata and a D1 binding, When the canonical ingest runs, Then it writes a durable receipt before accepting (44.1188ms)
✔ Given an existing D1 receipt, When identical content is persisted and read, Then the row is idempotent and retained (1.8799ms)
✔ Given migration 0003, When provenance storage is inspected, Then append-only receipt and derived source bindings are additive (1.9284ms)
✔ Given the durable Todo 8 receipt, When observed D1 hashes are audited, Then canonical, persisted, and readback hashes are explicit and equal (2.1843ms)
ℹ tests 21
ℹ suites 0
ℹ pass 21
ℹ fail 0
ℹ cancelled 0
ℹ skipped 0
ℹ todo 0
ℹ duration_ms 254.366
