✔ Given an accepted ingest, When provenance is persisted, Then its redacted canonical receipt remains queryable after the raw horizon (12.4366ms)
✔ Given four local whole-catalog runs, When capacity is evaluated without owner/live authority, Then local structure passes but production capacity is blocked (2.8716ms)
✔ Given accepted provenance metadata and a D1 binding, When the canonical ingest runs, Then it writes a durable receipt before accepting (38.8703ms)
✔ Given an existing D1 receipt, When identical content is persisted and read, Then the row is idempotent and retained (2.0072ms)
✔ Given migration 0003, When provenance storage is inspected, Then append-only receipt and derived source bindings are additive (2.0532ms)
ℹ tests 5
ℹ suites 0
ℹ pass 5
ℹ fail 0
ℹ cancelled 0
ℹ skipped 0
ℹ todo 0
ℹ duration_ms 226.4772
{
  "id": "task-08-happy",
  "verdict": "PASS",
  "actual_exit": 0,
  "assertions": [
    "provenance, quota math, overlap, backfill, and four-run cadence gates pass",
    "happy-path assertions pass on source-backed fixtures"
  ],
  "evidence": ".omo/evidence/seoul-gaja-v4-plan-review/task-8-happy.json"
}
