✔ Given malformed-input.json, When provenance or capacity proof is unsafe, Then policy fails closed (10.0845ms)
✔ Given manual-backfill-overlap.json, When provenance or capacity proof is unsafe, Then policy fails closed (2.5454ms)
✔ Given missing-live-cadence.json, When provenance or capacity proof is unsafe, Then policy fails closed (2.9489ms)
✔ Given missing-owner-quota.json, When provenance or capacity proof is unsafe, Then policy fails closed (4.2728ms)
✔ Given missing-provenance.json, When provenance or capacity proof is unsafe, Then policy fails closed (3.5183ms)
✔ Given prompt-injection.json, When provenance or capacity proof is unsafe, Then policy fails closed (8.7392ms)
✔ Given scheduled-overlap.json, When provenance or capacity proof is unsafe, Then policy fails closed (2.7374ms)
✔ Given single-canary.json, When provenance or capacity proof is unsafe, Then policy fails closed (2.3212ms)
✔ Given stale-state.json, When provenance or capacity proof is unsafe, Then policy fails closed (4.32ms)
✔ Given three-place-probe.json, When provenance or capacity proof is unsafe, Then policy fails closed (2.3226ms)
✔ Given unbounded-retry.json, When provenance or capacity proof is unsafe, Then policy fails closed (1.4618ms)
✔ Given an immutable receipt key, When different content is appended, Then the ledger rejects the overwrite (1.6574ms)
✔ Given an immutable D1 receipt key, When different content is persisted, Then storage rejects the overwrite (2.3808ms)
✔ Given accepted input without a D1 binding, When ingest reaches storage, Then it fails closed (39.4637ms)
ℹ tests 14
ℹ suites 0
ℹ pass 14
ℹ fail 0
ℹ cancelled 0
ℹ skipped 0
ℹ todo 0
ℹ duration_ms 238.7154
{
  "id": "task-08-failure",
  "verdict": "PASS",
  "actual_exit": 0,
  "assertions": [
    "provenance, quota math, overlap, backfill, and four-run cadence gates pass",
    "negative fixtures are rejected or produce the contracted fallback/NOT_RUN_BLOCKED verdict"
  ],
  "evidence": ".omo/evidence/seoul-gaja-v4-plan-review/task-8-failure.json"
}
