✔ tests\gates\task-08-contract.mjs (101.8663ms)
✔ Given malformed-input.json, When provenance or capacity proof is unsafe, Then policy fails closed (13.562ms)
✔ Given manual-backfill-overlap.json, When provenance or capacity proof is unsafe, Then policy fails closed (7.0295ms)
✔ Given missing-live-cadence.json, When provenance or capacity proof is unsafe, Then policy fails closed (2.5917ms)
✔ Given missing-owner-quota.json, When provenance or capacity proof is unsafe, Then policy fails closed (5.8389ms)
✔ Given missing-provenance.json, When provenance or capacity proof is unsafe, Then policy fails closed (4.5491ms)
✔ Given prompt-injection.json, When provenance or capacity proof is unsafe, Then policy fails closed (3.865ms)
✔ Given scheduled-overlap.json, When provenance or capacity proof is unsafe, Then policy fails closed (2.7621ms)
✔ Given single-canary.json, When provenance or capacity proof is unsafe, Then policy fails closed (5.4463ms)
✔ Given stale-state.json, When provenance or capacity proof is unsafe, Then policy fails closed (9.2574ms)
✔ Given three-place-probe.json, When provenance or capacity proof is unsafe, Then policy fails closed (3.8195ms)
✔ Given unbounded-retry.json, When provenance or capacity proof is unsafe, Then policy fails closed (2.3943ms)
✔ Given an immutable receipt key, When different content is appended, Then the ledger rejects the overwrite (1.7602ms)
✔ Given an immutable D1 receipt key, When different content is persisted, Then storage rejects the overwrite (2.6185ms)
✔ Given accepted input without a D1 binding, When ingest reaches storage, Then it fails closed (54.6453ms)
✔ Given an accepted ingest, When provenance is persisted, Then its redacted canonical receipt remains queryable after the raw horizon (25.361ms)
✔ Given four local whole-catalog runs, When capacity is evaluated without owner/live authority, Then local structure passes but production capacity is blocked (2.8383ms)
✔ Given accepted provenance metadata and a D1 binding, When the canonical ingest runs, Then it writes a durable receipt before accepting (49.4322ms)
✔ Given an existing D1 receipt, When identical content is persisted and read, Then the row is idempotent and retained (11.9221ms)
✔ Given migration 0003, When provenance storage is inspected, Then append-only receipt and derived source bindings are additive (7.7581ms)
ℹ tests 20
ℹ suites 0
ℹ pass 20
ℹ fail 0
ℹ cancelled 0
ℹ skipped 0
ℹ todo 0
ℹ duration_ms 301.5582
